欢迎使用Java进行软件构建。
Welcome to software construction in Java.
在我们的第一次朗读中，我们将
In this first reading we're going
来谈谈Java的一个重要特性，即
to talk about an important feature of Java that
使其有别于其他编程语言
makes it different from other programming languages
您可能已经学过了，比如Python和JavaScript。
you may have learned, like Python and JavaScript.
该功能称为静态类型。
That feature is called static typing.
接下来，我们将介绍本课程的三大目标。
From there, we'll introduce the three big goals of this course.
因为这门课程并不是真正的Java编程课程，
Because this course isn't really a Java programming course,
我们想学习如何编写好的代码
we want to learn how to write good code
用任何语言和三大理念
in any language and the three big ideas
是关于我们所说的好代码的意思。
are about what we mean by good code.
首先，它应该是安全的，不会有错误--或者换句话说，它应该是安全的
First it should be safe from bugs-- or in other words
正确--第二，应该很容易理解
correct-- two, it should be easy to understand
由其他程序员，第三，它
by other programmers, and three, it
应该准备好在未来被改变。
should be ready to be changed in the future.
本课程中的每个想法都将有助于实现这些目标。
Every idea in this course is going to help with these goals.
让我来介绍一下这门课程的阅读材料。
Let me also say something about the readings for this course.
阅读的每个部分都有一个正文部分
Each section of a reading has a text part
外加一个视频部分，在这个部分里，我基本上
plus a video part in which I basically
把课文通读一遍。
read through the text.
文本和视频在其中都具有相同的信息，
The text and the video both have the same information in them,
所以你可以忘了录像带
so you can just forget about the video
如果你愿意的话，只要读课文就行了
and just read the text if you prefer to do that
或者您可以在滚动的同时收听视频
or you can listen to the video while scrolling
或者你可以直接看视频
through the text or you can just watch the video
并在开始时忽略文本。
and ignore the text at first.
但如果您稍后需要参考该部分，
But if you need to refer back to the section later,
你可能会发现课文部分更容易些
you may find the text part easier
浏览、搜索和评论。
to skim and search and review.
好了，我们开始吧。
OK, let's get started.